

# **Tufan Recep SARI**

### Frontend Developer

+90 534 830 56 67



https://www.linkedin.com/in/tufan-sari/



tufanrsari@gmail.com



https://github.com/tufansari

#### **SUMMARY**

I have experience at web and mobile software languages. The software languages I know are as follows. I have focus on web frontend, so improving javascript's libraries, frameworks and trying to carry higher level. I also have experience in education. That's why I believe I'm good at relationships and communication with people. I will adapt to your vision and try to move forward. İn addition to, optimistic and personable individual enthusiastic about meeting new people. Strong presentation skills and a real researcher.

#### **CAREER**

- 11.10.2022
- 11.05.2022

**Smartpro Academy** 

#### WEB AND MOBILE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Learning languages about web and mobile.
  Making projects.
- Trainee.
- 2020-2021

## Museum of Illusions

#### **HUMAN RELATIONS OFFICER**

- Promotion of the museum to visitors.
- Answered questions, ensure the flow of people.
- 2019

#### **INSTRUCTOR**

**Brain Project** 

• About distraction prevention and good learning.

#### • 2017-2018

#### Capa Science High School

#### **TEACHER INTERN**

- Administered assessments to determine each student's specific edicational and social needs.
   Kept students on-task with proactive behavior modification and positive reinforcement strategies.
- Prepared quizzes, tests and examinations to gauge how well students were learning.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML | JavaScript | React.Js | CSS | Bootstrap | Vue.Js(lower level) | JSON | JSX | OOP | JQuery | AJAX | .NET | MVC | C# | MS SQL

#### **ONLINE COURSES**

C# Programming camp / Engin Demirog.

React, Redux and Hooks bootcamp/ Engin Demirog.

Web programming with React / Turkcell-Gelecegi Yazanlar.

#### **EDUCATION**

• 2019

#### **PEDAGOGY**

Marmara University • Master's Degree.

• 2014-2018

#### **BIOLOGY TEACHER EDUCATION**

Marmara University • Bachelor's Degree.

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### **ENGLISH**

- TALK
- Very Good.
- WRITING
- Advanced.

#### **TURKISH**

• Native Language.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate, Exam: Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure

#### **REFERENCES**

Orhan Umit Keskin – Product Manager at Kovan Studio

+90 (530) 667 06 19

Cihan Kilinckaya - General Manager at Museum of Illusions

+90 (532) 280 47 35

Tugay Aydin – Software Instructor at Smartpro Academy

+90 (542) 332 14 52